GABRIEL STEFANO VALIENTE

www.linkedin.com/in/gsvaliente | +34 617-016-774 | TIE: Y7395935T | gsvalient@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

Bilingual and multi-cultural college MBA graduate, with over 3 years of working experience in the United States, Spain, and El Salvador. Recently graduated from my MBA in International Business in Barcelona. Seeking opportunities to use and develop skills to achieve organizational objectives. Currently further extending my knowledge in social media community management. Interested in brand building and development, consumer research and trends, supply chain channels, and operations. Pursing my passion in Marketing and Logistics to make cross-function projects.

COMPETENCIES & SKILLS

- Native Spanish communication
- Cross-cultural marketing
- Customer analyses formulation
- International marketing (U.S., Spain, El Salvador)
- Digital marketing strategy & execution
- Paid digital media optimization
- Technologically capable

- Native English communication
- Microsoft Office Suite certified
- Sales & lead management
- Product launch campaign management
- Public relations management & execution
- Industry analyses & strategy formulation
- Teamwork oriented

WORK HISTORY

ALFA BETA CONSULTANTS

Marketing Associate | Barcelona, Spain | SEP 2020 - JUN 2021

- Supported creation of revised marketing strategy leveraging digital to respond to new COVID-19 operating reality.
- Developed digital marketing strategy and manage execution of paid and owned media including Google AdWords, website, and other platforms.
- Created paid digital marketing guidelines for franchised system to strengthen and optimize paid efforts across franchisees.
- Led creation of development strategy seeking new revenue streams for Aclam, a guitar company, looking to expand sources of income.
- Created execution roadmap of development strategy for Aclam including timetables, accountabilities and requirements to successfully expand revenues.

GLOBALPAY SERVICES

Marketing and Sales Coordinator | San Salvador, El Salvador | JUN 2018 - SEP 2019

- Assisted in increasing 15% of application user base by increasing media outlets
- Managed Digital Marketing campaigns, with a focus on social media
- Cultivated relationships with new and potential customers to build leads
- Executed product launch for top-up application for the company
- Enhanced cost structure of sim card distribution to increase revenues

THE POWER GROUP

Account Coordinator | Dallas, TX, USA | OCT 2016 - FEB 2018

• Launched social media campaigns for agency clients with set KPIs

- Optimized website for customers through SEO and Google AdWords
- Organized campaigns for openings and activations
- Developed an industry analysis of competitors for strategy development
- Formed press releases and radio interviews

NASHER SCULPTURE CENTER

Digital Marketing Intern | Dallas, TX, USA | SUMMER 2017

MERCEDES-BENZ

Digital Marketing Intern | San Salvador, El Salvador | SUMMER 2014

EDUCATION

MASTER'S IN SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGEMENT Barcelona Formación Barcelona, Spain | ONGOING

MBA IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS

EU Business School

Barcelona, Spain | JUNE 2020

BA IN MARKETING
West Virgina University
Morgantown, WV | MAY 2016